"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
就是你这个混蛋 杀了我孩子
You're the son of a bitch who shot my kid.
把他抬起来 送去泉水那里
Pick him up. Get him to the spring.
你在帮倒忙! 快淹死他了!
You're not saving him! You're drowning him!
你朋友死了
Your friend is dead.
Jack啊!
Jack!
发生什么事了?
What happened?
你要干嘛?
What is it you want?
我什么秘密都没有 你干嘛这样对我?
I don't have any secrets. Why are you doing this?
啊!
Aah!
- 你得把这药给你的朋友  - 这里面是什么?
- You have to give your friend this pill.  - What is in it?
- 毒药  - 你们为何想杀Sayid?
- Poison.  - Why would you people wanna kill Sayid?
他体内有股暗黑势力 正在滋长
There is a darkness growing in him.
一旦到达心脏 你曾经的朋友
And once it reaches his heart, everything your friend once was
就会消失了
will be gone.
你有什么事瞒着我?
What are you hiding from me?
那药是毒药 他们想借我的手杀了你
The pill was poison. They wanted me to kill you.
你不下车 计价器可会一直计费呢 兄弟
The meter doesn't stop until you get out, pal.
不用找了
Keep the change.
是Sayid啊
Sayid.
你好 Nadia
Hello, Nadia.
你来了!
You're here!
你到哪儿去了 Sayid叔叔?
Where were you, Uncle Sayid?
- 我去了趟悉尼  - 悉尼在哪里?
- I was in Sydney.  - Where's Sydney?
在澳大利亚
In Australia.
你那花 是要送给我太太的?
You bring flowers for my wife?
如果你想要的话 我就送给你
I'll give them to you, if you want.
很高兴见到你 Sayid
It's good to see you, Sayid.
- 我也很高兴见到你 哥哥  - 走 屋里坐
- It's good to see you, too, brother.  - Come.
Sayid叔叔 你从澳大利亚 给我们带了什么礼物?
Uncle Sayid, what did you bring us from Australia?
去我的包里看看 在沙发那儿
Go look in my bag. It's on the couch.
你能回来真好 Sayid 他们想死你了
It's good you came, Sayid. They've missed you.
他能现身 就不错了...
We're lucky he even showed up...
环球旅行者结束了异国之旅
The world traveler off on his exotic business trips.
为一家石油公司做合同翻译
Translating contracts for an oil company
算不上什么异国之旅... 而且极其枯燥
is hardly exotic... And it's painfully dull.
干洗生意... 做起来也是有一定风险存在的
There's... there's a little adventure in the world of dry cleaning.
他只是在谦虚而已 Omer刚开了家新店
He's being modest. Omer's just opened up a new store.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我以为我们以前说过 吃饭的时候 不接电话
I thought we talked about cell phones at the dinner table.
先吃到这里吧 有事
Dinner is over. This is business.
喂?
Yes?
你收到我的信了么?
Did you get my letters?
嗯
Yes.
可是你没回信
You never wrote back.
这些真是太棒了! 谢谢!
These are awesome! Thanks!
别客气
You're welcome.
妈妈 我们在Sayid叔叔的包里 找到了一张你的照片
Mommy, we found a picture of you in Uncle Sayid's bag.
我想跟你谈谈
I want to talk to you.
我一肚子疑问 有待解惑
I want some answers.
解什么惑?
Answers to what?
我们从那台机器开始说起
Let's start with that machine.
你们把我绑在这东西上
You hooked me up to this thing,
还扎了我几针
you stuck needles in me,
你说这是一个测试
and you called it a test.
各人心中一杆秤
For every man, there is a scale.
秤的一边 是善
On one side of the scale, there is good.
另一边... 是恶
On the other side... evil.
这台机器告诉我们
This machine tells us
秤的平衡度如何
how the scale is balanced.
而你的秤...
And yours...
倾斜向了错误的一边
tipped the wrong way.
这就是你要毒死我的原因?
And that's why you tried to poison me?
没错
Yes.
我觉得 你死了会比较好
I think it would be best if you were dead.
你以为你了解我 实际上大错特错
You think you know me, but you don't.
我是个好人
I'm a good man.
所以 如果你想杀我... 啊!
So if you're trying to kill me... Uhh!
你走吧
Go.
离开这儿
Leave this place.
别回来了
Never come back.
你准备好了么?
Are you ready?
为什么让我去?
Why does it have to me be?
我是说 你可以让Sawyer或Jin或...
I mean, you could send Sawyer or Jin or...
- 自己去做  - 如果我可以自己解决的话
- do it yourself.  - If I could do it myself,
我不会来找你 Claire
I wouldn't be asking you, Claire.
如果我去的话
If I go in there,
我必须确保 你能实践诺言
I need to know you'll do what you said.
我要找回我的儿子
I want my son back.
我会信守诺言的
I always do what I say.
你会伤害他们吗?
Are you gonna hurt them?
我只会对那些不听话的人下手
Only the ones who won't listen.
迷失 第6季第6集
是我
It's me.
- 冷静点儿  - 你要干嘛?
- Calm down.  - What are you doing?
现在是凌晨2点半
It's 2:30 the morning.
Sayid 我有麻烦了
Sayid, I'm in trouble.
什么麻烦?
What kind of trouble?
第二家店 我是借钱开的
I borrowed money to open the second store.
但...
But...
我不是从银行借的
I didn't borrow it from the bank.
我还完钱后
I paid the loan back,
债主却...
but the man who lent me this money...
他说 我还欠他每个月的利息没还...
He says I still owe him interest every month...
我的店开多久 就得按月支付他多久的利息
for as long as I own my business.
如果你缺钱 我可以借给你...
If you need money, I'll lend it to you...
我不需要钱 Sayid
I don't need money, Sayid.
我要你去说服这些人 别再来找我的麻烦
I need you to convince these people to leave me alone.
- "说服"他们?  - Sayid 别忘了你在跟谁说话
- "Convince" them?  - Sayid, don't forget who you're talking to.
我知道你打仗的时候做过什么
I know what you did in the war.
你曾是共和国卫队的审讯官
You were an interrogator for the Republican Guard.
我知道你的底细
I know what kind of man you are.
如果你以为
If you think I'm going to hurt someone
光凭你商业决策失误 我就会去害人...
just because you made a bad business decision...
听我说 这不光是我一个人的麻烦!
Look, this is not about me!
我们毕生的储蓄... 全没了 Sayid 什么都没了
Our life savings... it's all gone, Sayid. All of it.
我们可能连房子都保不住
We could lose our home.
拜托了
Please.
听着... 我知道你很在乎Nadia
Look... I know you care about Nadia.
如果你还在乎我们... 在乎她...
If you care about us... about her...
你会去的 Sayid
you will do this, Sayid.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我早已脱胎换骨了
I'm not that man anymore.
你要干嘛?
What are you doing?
我要走了
I'm leaving.
他们赶我走
I've been banished.
赶你走? 为什么?
Banished? For what?
很明显 我是个不祥之人
Apparently, I'm evil.
这些人说 我最好一死了之...
These people say I'm better off dead...
虽然这听上去让人不敢置信
Which is surprising,
毕竟是他们救了我一命
considering they were the ones who saved my life.
呃 事实上 你不是他们救活的 他们...
Well, actually, they're not. They...
他们试过要救你 但...
They tried to save you, but...
你最后还是死了 兄弟
you were dead, man.
死了2个小时
For two hours.
相信我 当... 当... 当你坐起来的时候
Trust me, when... when... when you sat up,
他们跟我们一样吃惊
they were just as surprised as the rest of us.
不管究竟是什么把你救活的 反正不是他们
So whatever brought you back, it wasn't them.
别动
Hold it.
停! 别开枪!
Stop! Don't shoot her!
你来这儿干嘛?
What are you doing here?
他想见你
He wants to see you.
说英文
Speak English.
谁想见我?
Who wants to see me?
你知道是谁
You know who.
如果他想见我 叫他自己来
If he wants to see me, then tell him to come in.
不 他要你去找他
No, he wants you to go to him.
他就在墙外面等着
He's waiting outside beyond the outer wall.
我不傻
I'm not a fool.
如果我走出这所寺庙...
If I step outside this temple...
他就会杀了我
he'll kill me.
嗯 那你也许该派个 他不会杀的人去
Well, then maybe you should send someone he won't kill.
拦住她!
Stop her!
把这个女孩关到山洞里去 事情解决后再说
Put the girl in the hole until this is resolved.
立刻带Shephard和Reyes去我房间
Then bring Shephard and Reyes to my room immediately.
啊 那有点儿困难
Ah, that's gonna be a little difficult.
他们失踪了
We can't find them.
快去找!
走!
Come on!
跟我来
Come with me.
我以为你希望我离开这儿
I thought you wanted me to leave.
事情有变
Things have changed.
你的朋友... Shephard和Reyes...
Your friends... Shephard and Reyes...
你知道他们去哪儿了吗?
do you know where they went?
不 我不知道
No, I don't.
Claire为什么在这儿?
Why is Claire here?
她说的话是什么意思?
And what was she talking about?
她被一个愤怒的人
She's a confused girl,
迷惑了
under the influence of an angry man.
谁?
What man?
多年来
For years,
他受困于此
he has been trapped.
但现在Jacob去世了
But now Jacob's gone.
他就自由了
He's free.
这个人 不摧毁岛上的一切生灵
This man will not stop until he has destroyed
是不会罢休的
every living thing on this island.
他是恶魔的化身
He is evil incarnate.
你想让我去和他交涉?
And you want me to speak to him?
不
No.
我希望你干掉他
I want you to kill him.
他会扮成你认识的某人...
He will come to you as someone you know...
死去的某人
Someone who has died.
你一见到他...
As soon as you see him...
就把这个深深插进他的胸口
plunge this deep into his chest.
如果你等他开口说话之后
If you allow him to speak,
那就来不及了
it is already too late.
自打我来到这里
Since I've been here,
你们淹我 打我 折磨我
I've been drowned, beaten and tortured at your hands.
我为什么还要帮你做事?
Why would I ever do anything for you?
你自己说 你是个好人
You said that there is still good in your soul.
那就证明给我看
Then prove it.
嘿 等等我!
Hey, wait up!
Sayid叔叔 你会待多久?
How long are you staying, Uncle Sayid?
还待几天
Just a few more days.
我得去多伦多...
I have to go to Toronto...
工作
to work.
我们喜欢你在这里
We like it when you're here.
是的 妈妈也喜欢
Yeah, and mommy likes it, too.
好的 乖乖的
Okay. Be good.
Sayid啊!
Sayid!
Omer啊!
Omer!
我的丈夫还好吗?
Is my husband going to be all right?
我们马上就给他动手术
We're taking him into surgery now.
- 他的肺被刺穿 并伴有大出血  - 到底怎么回事 你知道吗?
- He's suffered a punctured lung and some internal bleeding.  - Do you know how this happened?
急救队认为 他遇到了劫匪
E.M.T.s think he was mugged.
他的情况一稳定下来 我立即通知你们
I'll come get you as soon as he's stable.
- Sayid! 你去哪儿?  - 待在这里陪Omer
- Sayid! Where are you going?  - Stay here with Omer.
这不是打劫 对吧?
This wasn't a mugging, was it?
不管你想干什么...
Whatever you're thinking of doing...
别那么做
don't do it.
我不想你那样
I don't want you to.
求你了... 就...
Please... Just...
回家吧
go home.
去等孩子们
Wait for the kids.
让他们感受到安全 Sayid
Make them feel safe, Sayid.
行吗?
Will you do that?
嘿?
Hello?
是Sayid?
Sayid?
你好 Kate
Hello, Kate.
你要走吗?
Are you leaving?
我也不是很确定
I am not exactly sure.
我错过了什么?
What'd I miss?
问Miles吧
Ask Miles.
谢谢
Thank you.
哇
Wow.
很高兴见到你 Miles
It's good to see you, too, Miles.
Sawyer让你回来打包 是吧?
Sawyer sent you packing, huh?
我也想跟他走
I thought about going after him, too.
但是 呃 我知道 我要是不回来
But, um, I knew he'd just end up berating me
他会一直骂我
until I turned around and came back.
发生了很多事情吧?
That pretty much what happened?
很多
Pretty much.
呃...
Well...
欢迎归队
Welcome back to the circus.
- 这里发生了什么事?  - 呃 我想下...
- What's going on in here?  - Well, let's see...
噢 那个澳大利亚小妞回来了
Oh, that Australian chick's back.
等下 什么?
Wait. What?
你知道的 那个... 那个金发的... 有过孩子的小妞
You know, the... the blonde... one that had the baby.
是Claire?
Claire?
对的 Claire
Right. Claire.
她几个小时前刚回来的
She just strolled in here a couple hours ago,
举止怪异
acting all weird.
不过 还是很辣
Still hot, though.
Miles 她在哪?
Miles, where is she?
她在哪?
Where is she?
你好 Sayid
Hello, Sayid.
你为什么要这么做?
Now why'd you go and do that?
你想拿回它?
You want it back?
拿着 我不吃人
Take it. I won't bite.
你是什么东西?
What are you?
呃 Sayid 你好像有所耳闻
Well, Sayid, you seem to have some idea about that,
所以连招呼都不打
considering that you stabbed me in the chest
就直接刺我胸口
without even saying hello.
他们跟你说了什么?
What did they tell you?
他们说你是恶魔的化身
They said you were evil incarnate.
我为你感到悲哀
I feel sorry for you.
为什么?
Why?
Dogen... 让你来这儿的那个人...
Dogen... the man who sent you out here...
知道你根本杀不了我
knew that you had no chance of killing me.
而且他认为 你一旦动手 我就会杀了你
And he believed that I would kill you if you tried.
而且这不是他第一次
And this wasn't the first time that
借刀杀人 对吧?
he tried to get someone else to do it for him, was it?
嗯
No.
那你这么容易就信他的话 真悲哀
Then shame on you for being talked into it so easily.
那你想让我信你什么?
And what is it you are trying to talk me into?
什么?
Sorry?
你没杀我
You haven't killed me.
很明显 你有目的
Clearly, there's something you want.
我只想让你带个口信儿 仅此而已
I just want you to deliver a message, that's all.
你怎么不让Claire传话?
Then why didn't you just have Claire deliver it?
因为你才有说服力
Because it would mean a lot more coming from you.
Sayid 如果你能帮我的话...
Sayid, if you'll do this for me...
要是我告诉你 你能得到一切你想要的东西呢?
What if I told you that you could have anything you wanted?
要是我告诉你 你能得到这世上任何东西呢?
What if I said you could have anything in the entire world?
那我就会说 我唯一想要的人
I would tell you that the only thing I ever wanted
死在了我怀里
died in my arms.
我永远都见不到她了
And I'll never see it again.
但要是你能呢?
But what if you could?
哦...
Uh...
出了点小意外
We had an unfortunate incident
被飞去来器打成这样的
involving a boomerang.
是我的错
My apologies.
孩子们什么时候睡的?
Oh, what time did the kids go to bed?
大概两小时前
About two hours ago.
你怎么跟他们说的?
And what did you tell them?
爸爸出了点意外
Daddy had an accident,
但他不会有事的
but that he's going to be fine.
他还在术后恢复中 但是...
He's still recovering from surgery, but...
他现在醒了
he's awake now.
他告诉你借贷的事了?
Did he tell you about the loan?
听着 我有钱
Look, I have money.
不
No.
这是Omer的过错
This is Omer's responsibility.
他得自己承担责任
He brought this on himself.
你为什么不想跟我在一起?
Why didn't you want to be with me?
Sayid 你把我的照片一直带在身上
You carry my picture around with you, Sayid.
你要是关心我
If you care about me,
为什么还把我推向你哥哥?
why did you push me towards your brother?
在过去的12年里
For the last 12 years,
我一直试着洗净双手...
I've been trying to wash my hands...
洗净我做过的丑事
of all the horrible things I've done.
我不能跟你在一起...
I can't be with you...
因为我不配得到你
because I don't deserve you.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
丛林里有个男人...
There is a man in the jungle...
在往南大约一英里的
about a mile south of us,
围墙边上
by the outer wall.
他让我回来捎个口信
He sent me back here to give you a message.
他想让你们知道 Jacob已经死了
He wants you to know that Jacob is dead.
因为他死了
And because he's gone,
你们也没必要再待下去了
none of you have to stay here any longer.
你们自由了
You're free.
我碰到的这个人
The man that I met
马上就要永远地离开这个岛
is leaving the island forever.
想要跟他走的
And those of you who want to go with him
就离开寺庙 跟他一起走
should leave the temple and join him.
日落前 做出决定吧
You have until sundown to decide.
要是日落时 我们留下来呢?
What happens at sundown if we stay?
那就只有死路一条
You die.
嘿!
Hey!
你什么时候回来的? Ford和Kwon跟你在一起吗?
When did you get back? Are Ford and Kwon with you?
Claire在哪?
Where is Claire?
好吧 我需要你先回答我的问题...
Okay, I need you to tell me what I need to know before I...
我问你 Claire在哪?
I said, where is Claire?
好吧 先放开我 行吗?
All right. Just let go of me, okay?
给你两分钟
You have two minutes.
# ... 褪色 #
# ... fade away #
# 抓住一颗陨星 放进你的口袋 #
# Catch a falling star and put it in your pocket #
# 下雨天再拿出来 #
# Save it for a rainy day #
# 因为爱会来轻触你肩 #
# For love may come and tap you on the shoulder #
# 星稀的夜晚 #
# Some starless night #
- Claire吗?  - # 它们就在... #
- Claire?  - # They are just in... #
Claire 是我
Claire, it's me.
Kate吗?
Kate?
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我... 简直不敢相信你在这儿
I... I can't believe you're here.
他们也抓你了?
Did they capture you, too?
不 没有 他们...
No. No, they...
为什么他们把你关在下面?
Why did they put you down here?
发生什么事了?
What happened?
Kate 他们抓了我儿子 他们抓了Aaron
They have my son, Kate. They have Aaron.
- 他们把他从我身边带走  - 不 不
- They took him from me.  - No. No.
Claire 他们没抓Aaron
Claire, they don't have Aaron.
是我带走他的
I took him.
我...
I...
什么?
What?
我把他带出了岛
I took him off the island.
那时你走了 我们找不到你
You were gone, and we couldn't find you.
所以...
So...
我养了他
I raised him.
还有...
And...
他是最动人 最美丽的小男孩
He is the most beautiful, amazing little boy.
然后我回来救你
But I came back here to rescue you
这样你就可以和他在一起
so that you could be with him,
这样你们就可以又相聚了
so that you guys could be together again.
Kate 我不需要你救
I'm not the one that needs to be rescued, Kate.
时间到 走吧
Time's up. Let's go.
别! 别! 等一下!
No! No! Wait!
- 别! 等等! 等一下!  - 你都见到她了
- No! Wait! Wait!  - You wanted to see her.
那就走吧
So let's go.
Kate 他来了
He's coming, Kate.
他来了 他们阻止不了他!
He's coming, and they can't stop him!
大家伙儿 冷静点儿! 没事儿的
Eeverybody, calm down! It's going to be okay.
别! 别! 等一下!
No! No! Wait!
等会儿!
Hang on!
嘿!
Hey!
嘿 你制造了恐慌 我们的人都打算走了
Hey, you created a panic here. Our people are leaving.
别人请我来捎个口信而已
I was asked to deliver a message,
受人之托 忠人之事
and that's what I did.
你的人干什么 全由他们自己
What your people do now is up to them.
Cindy 等等嘛 你们在这儿会很安全
Cindy, just wait. You're all safe here.
我们只要待在寺庙里 他就碰不到我们
As long as we stay in the temple, he can't touch us.
你听见他说的了 Jacob死了
You heard him. Jacob's dead.
如果这里不安全了
And if it isn't safe here anymore,
我们就不能冒险留下
we can't take that risk.
大家听着!
Everyone, listen!
这是造谣!
This is a bluff!
他进不来! 他进不来的!
He can't come in! He can't come in!
嘿 出什么事了? 前一分钟 你被赶出去了
Hey, what happened out there? One minute, you're banished,
下一分钟 你说大家都会死
the next you're telling everyone they're gonna die.
总结得好
That's the sum of it.
- 那我们是要走 还是干嘛?  - 没到时候
- So are we getting out of here or what?  - Not yet.
我必须把这还了
I have to return this.
来接孩子?
Going to pick up the kids?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
干嘛不上车呢?
Why don't you get in the car?
Sayid 上车
Get in, Sayid.
除非你想我们一起去接孩子?
干嘛不坐?
Why don't you have a seat?
嘿 吃鸡蛋吗?
Hey, you want some eggs?
我能 呃...
I can, uh...
做你想要的... 煎鸡蛋 炒鸡蛋
make whatever you want... fried, scrambled.
呃 我们还有锅吗? 那锅在哪?
Uh, we still got that poacher? Where's the poacher?
你想要荷包蛋吗? 我做得挺好吃的
You want poached? Cause I could make you some good poached eggs.
不 谢了
No, thank you.
我做鸡蛋超好的
I make good eggs.
不来点吗?
No?
好吧
All right.
我叫Martin Keamy
Martin Keamy.
Sayid Jarrah 你已经知道了
Sayid Jarrah, but you already know that.
噢 那个 我知道 是的
Uh, that, I do. Yeah.
好
Right.
那么...
So...
Sayid啊...
Sayid...
你哥哥怎么样?
How's your brother doin'?
他的哥哥被打劫了
His brother got mugged
就在他自己的店门口
right out front of his own store.
这真是... 太惨了
It was just... terrible.
不过 这样一来 你知道
Well, but at least this way, you know,
你就可以 继续照顾他的家人了
you're still around to take care of his family.
你确实想要照顾他的家人 不是吗?
You do want to take care of his family, don't you?
承认了?
Yes?
你知道 我能看出来 你是一个很... 直爽的人 Sayid
You know, I can see that you're a very... direct guy, Sayid,
所以我也就直奔主题了
So I'm just gonna get to the point.
你的哥哥... 他向我借了些钱
Your brother... he borrowed some money from me,
就像其他人
and just like anybody,
就像那些借钱的 和还钱的人一样
who borrows money or has a loan to pay,
他欠了钱 就得还
he has to make payments.
我哥哥告诉我 他能还的 都已经还给你了
My brother told me he's paid you everything he owes,
但是你还不知足
but that you still want more.
Sayid 他骗了你 你哥哥确实欠我的
Sayid, that's a lie. You brother does owe me,
而且必须得有人 来还那些钱
and somebody is gonna pay me that money.
是你让我哥哥住院的吗?
Did you put my brother in the hospital?
噢 你认为是我干的?
Oh, you think it was me?
不是我
I didn't do that.
你知道 这是一个危险的世界 Sayid
You know, it's a dangerous world, Sayid.
你对此一清二楚 因为你来自伊拉克
and you know that because you're from Iraq.
你永远也不知道 有人要偷袭...
You never know when somebody's just gonna sneak up...
啊!
Uhh!
噢!
喔 喔 喔 喔 喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sayid啊...
Sayid...
- 好 别紧张  - 闭嘴
- Okay, just relax now.  - Shut up.
好 好的
Okay. Fine.
好 好 这事就算了
Fine. Okay, it's done.
好吗?
All right?
你... 哥哥不欠我什么了
Y... your brother doesn't owe me anything.
一笔勾销 好吗?
The debt's forgiven, all right?
好吗? 行不?
Good? Okay?
放轻松... 忘记这件事
Just relax and... forget about it.
我忘不了
I can't.
啊!
Uhh!
警告: 严禁开门
你是谁?
Who are you?
我不懂英语
No English.
你让他和你说话了
You let him talk to you.
我照你说的 在他的胸上刺了一刀
I stabbed him in the chest like you told me to.
然后我才让他和我说话
Then I let him talk to me.
这已经是你第二次 想借刀杀人
That's twice you've tried to have someone else kill me.
你本来有机会自己动手的
You had the opportunity to do it yourself.
为什么没杀我?
Why didn't you?
我以前是一个生意人...
I was a businessman once...
在大阪
In Osaka.
我在一家银行工作
I worked at a bank.
我的工作干得很好
I was good at my job,
很成功
Very successful.
然后一个星期五
And one Friday,
我升职了
I was promoted.
我的同事和我一起出去庆祝
My associates took me out to celebrate.
我喝了很多酒
I had too much to drink.
每个星期五...
Every Friday...
我会去棒球场接我儿子
I picked my son up from baseball.
他那时12岁
He was 12.
事故很严重
The accident was very bad.
我活下来了
I survived.
但是我儿子...
But my son...
后来...
And then...
在医院里...
in the hospital...
一个男人找到我...
a man came to me...
我从来没有见过他
A man I had never met.
他告诉我
And he told me that
他可以救回我儿子
he could save my son's life,
但是我必须到这个岛上来
But I would have to come here to this island,
在这里 我会有一份新工作
where I would have a new job.
而且我再也不能见到我儿子
And I could never see my boy again.
这个人是谁?
Who was this man?
他叫Jacob
His name was Jacob.
Jacob做的这个交易很苛刻
Jacob drives a hard bargain.
外面的那个人...
The man outside...
我想 他和你做了一个类似的交易?
I take it he offered you a similar bargain?
是的
Yes.
太阳下山了
It is sundown.
你是选择留下 还是离开?
Will you choose to stay or go?
留下
I'd like to stay.
啊!
Aah!
噢 天哪!
Oh, my God!
你都做了些什么?!
What have you done?!
你知道你刚才都做了什么吗?!
Do you realize what you just did?!
他是唯一能把它挡在外面的人!
He was the only thing keeping it out!
白痴!
Idiot!
你把它放进来了!
You just let it in!
呃!
Uhh!
我知道
I know.
我们得走了
We gotta go now.
啊!
Aah!
快跑! 快跑!
Run! Run!
这边!
This way!
这边! 走这边!
This way! This way!
我必须带上Claire
I have to go get Claire.
Shephard和Reyes 还有Ford 在哪?
Where are Shephard and Reyes and Ford?
你他妈是谁?
Who the hell are you?
回答问题
Just answer the question.
他们走了 所有人都走了 我是唯一留下的
They're gone. Everyone's gone. I'm the only one left.
Kate和我走散了 Lapidus? 你怎么...
Kate and I got separated. Lapidus? How did you...
我们马上就会被追上
We'll play catch-up later.
你想活命 最好现在就跑路
You want to live, you better move your ass.
Jarrah怎么办? 他在这儿吗?
What about Jarrah? Is he here?
- 是的 他到泉水池那儿去了  - 我去找他
- Yeah, he was headed to the pool room.  - I'll go get him.
Linus 等等!
Linus, wait!
好 其他人 跟我走 快点
All right, the rest of you, with me. Come on.
Claire 快来! Claire 我们得走了
Claire, come on! Claire, we gotta go.
- 你赶快出来  - 不
- You gotta get out of there.  - No.
- 什么?!  - 在这里面会更安全
- What?!  - You'll be much safer here.
Sayid啊?
Sayid?
走吧
Come on.
我知道一条出去的路
I know a way out of here.
还来得及
There's still time.
我不走
Not for me.
你的丈夫在哪里?
Where's your husband?
- 什么?!  - 你丈夫昨天离开这里的
- What?!  - Your husband took off yesterday.
- Jin在这里? 他还活着?  - 至少我上次看到他 还活着
- Jin was here? He's alive?  - Last I saw him, yeah.
你应该听到了 是吧?
You do hear that, right?
你有对策了 还是要一直盯着墙看?
You got a plan or you gonna keep staring at the wall?
是的 我有对策了
Yes, I have a plan.
大家都进去
Everybody inside now.